MOHSEN KOORANI MASKAN

AeroSpace Engineer & Back-end Developer

CONTACT

- Raraj, Alborz, Iran
- +98 26 3232 2604 (Home) +98 910 988 3120 (Mobile)
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ /MohsenKooraniMaskan
- https://KevinKoorani.github.io/
- MKM.Koorani@Outlook.com

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

C#

WPF

.Net (Framework/Core)

Entity Framework / Core

ASP.Net (MVC/Core) - WebApi

OOP and Solid Principles

Design Patterns

SOL Server

UML & Data Modeling

StimulSoft

Unit & end2end Testing

Python

Git

HTML & CSS

Angular

Matlab

Maple

C / C++

Fortran



PROFILE

Back-end developer with over 4 years of experience in an top notch organization and a creative person with the ability of managing the projects and participate in teamworks. Skilled in C#, SQL Server, UML Modeling, Familiar with the implementation of human resource processes and very eager to learn new technologies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

PENDAR IDEAS BackEnd Developer

2018 - present

I'm honored to work as a part of such a awesome team from all over Iran. my tasks and achievements are:

- -Design and development of a framework for generating reports using StimulSoft.
- -Design and development of various reports for human resource management applications. (Logics and corresponding output in StimulSoft).
- -Design and development of a windows application to extract data from time attendance devices (different types of devices) and upload into the company's product database.
- -Improve company's old designs and development of company products.
- -Management of servers and databases of the company's products.
- -Create UML models of company products by MagicDraw.
- -Write e2e tests with selenium framework and unit tests for different parts of the company's products.

EDUCATION

K. N. T. Univesity of Technology Tehran, Iran Master of Structural Engineering Final Score: 17.87/20 2017 - 2020 Urmia University of Technology Urmia, Iran Bachelor of AeroSpace Engineering Final Score: 16.31/20 2013 - 2017

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

K. N. T. Univesity of Technology Tehran, Iran Teacher Assistant Msc of AeroSpace Engineering -Advanced Structural Dynamics -Advanced Structural Analysis

- -Advanced Composite Structures
- -Advanced Finite Element Methods
- -Mechanics of Materials

K. N. T. Univesity of Technology Tehran, Iran

Teacher

- -Python Programming
- -MATLAB Programming
- -Abagus Software
- -Catia Software

MOHSEN KOORANI MASKAN

AeroSpace Engineer & Back-end Developer



Languages

Persian (Native)

English



SKILLS

Creativity

Leadership

Organization

Teamwork

Initiative

Abaqus

Ansys

Fluent

Catia

Solid Works

Comsol Muliphysics

Microsoft Office

Gambit

Nastran - Patran

Open Foam

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Indesign



More Info

Birth: 1994

Military Service Status:

Exemptions for special cases

Requested salary per month: 100,000,000 Rials

ACADEMIC

AeroSpace Engineer with a master's degree from Khajeh Nasir University of Technology with more than 3 years of work experience in the field of aerospace and fluent in related software.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

ARIA SABOKBAL Designer

2014 - 2017

I'm honored to work as designer and after 2 years as the head of design department. my tasks and achievements are:

-Scientific design and production of various parts of light aircraft (2 to 8 people).

HONORS

- Secretary of the association of Inventors and Researchers of urmia university of technology, 2015 - 2017.
- Ranked 3rd in the class of 2013, Aerospace Engineering Dept. of urmia university of technology.
- Ranked 1st in the class of 2017, Aerospace Engineering Structural Engineering Dept. of K. N. T. university of technology.
- Bsc Thesis: Improving diesel engine performance by controlling cavitation in injector nozzles (analysis by Ansys - Fluent commercial software).
- Msc Thesis: Progressive damages analysis due to mechanical and thermal loads on composite laminates (analysis by Abaqus commercial software and a general and innovative python script for simulate progress of damage and failure).

W OTHER EXPERIENCES

- Aerodynamics project: Implementation of Analysis of flow on cylinders and airfoils by panel method by Matlab.
- Computational fluid dynamics project: Implementation of heat transfer analysis at different speeds and boundary conditions by Matlab.
- Heat transfer project: Implementation of heat transfer analysis in different specimens and conditions by Comsol and Matlab.
- Industrial design project: Theoretical design of quadcopter by Catia.
- Advanced industrial design project: Theoretical design of turbo-fan engine by Catia.
- Advanced composite structures project: Analyse progress of failure in composite structures by Python and Matlab.
- Advanced finite element method project: Implementation of general structure analysis process using finite element method by Python and Matlab.
- Aeroelastic project: Analysis of instability and divergence of aircraft structure at variable altitude by Python, Maple and Matlab.
- Optimization project: Implementation of genetic algorithms and other optimization algorithms (such as BFGS, DFP, FR, etc ...) by Python and Matlab.
- Full design of a pioneer UAV (both generalized and detailed).